Guide to the Riggs Family papers, 1672-2006 MS2239
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Photographs and prints, circa 1800 - circa 1948; Series 1; 15.75 Linear Feet
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of Mary J. Bright in her wedding gown, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 64, Item 2)
  - Glass plate negative: unidentified group portrait, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 64, Item 3)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of Lawrason Riggs, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 64, Item 4)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of unidentified man, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 64, Item 5)
  - Glass plate negative: house by a lake, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 64, Item 6)
  - Glass plate negative: house and unidentified people, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 64, Item 7)
  - Glass plate negative: portrait of Alice Lawrason Riggs, circa 1800; Series 1 (Box 64, Item 8)
- Personal artifacts, circa 1672 - circa 1920; Series 2; 9 Linear Feet
  Personal artifacts include religious books, handwritten books, artwork and personal accessories. The bulk of the material dates between circa 1880- circa 1920. Books include "Baxter's Christian Directory" from 1672, a German Bible from 1683, a Bible from 1851, and memo books from R.C. Riggs (1923) and E. Francis Riggs Sr. Artwork consists of two oil paintings of George Washington Riggs (1880-1883), Katie Riggs' 1883 sketchbook of San Remo, some portrait sketches of unknown individuals, a framed pen and ink cartoon personifying Alaska and the Philippines, and a woodcut portrait of Rodin by Rene Cheruy. Personal artifacts include three pipes, a pocket watch, a pair of white leather gloves, and Thomas Lawrason Riggs' medic armband worn in World War I.
  - Baxter's Christian Directory, 1672; Series 2 (Box 17, Object 1)
    General
    Binding broken. John Beverley Riggs' notes: "The Baxter's Directory with early records of family in it." "Family entries appear on these pages: +1, 3, 41, 208, 294, 327, 470, 474, 475, 560, 568, 586, 615, 668, 670, 672, 730, 768, 769, 770, 779, 930, 932." JBR (18 July '89)
  - German Bible, 1683; Series 2 (Box 18, Object 1)
    Binding broken. Belonged to John Adams, father of Katherine Adams Riggs.
  - Holy Bible, 1851; Series 2 (Box 19, Object 1)
  - "The Family Tree" genealogy book, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Object 1)
  - Sketchbook: "Katie Riggs-1883-San Remo", Series 2 (Box 20, Object 2)
  - Elisha Francis Riggs Sr. memo book, undated; Series 2 (Box 20, Object 3)
  - Oil painting: George Washington Riggs (1880-1883), signed Stephen Hill Parker, undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Object 1)
  - Oil painting: George Washington Riggs (1880-1883), Series 2 (Box 21, Object 2)
  - Sketch: Man in uniform (ERF Jr?), 1918; Series 2 (Box 21, Object 3)
  - Sketch: "Mt. Riggs/ elevation 9922 ft" possibly by Katie Riggs, undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Object 4)
  - Sketch: Man with pipe, signed EWG., undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Object 5)
  - Sketch: Man in glasses, signed EWG, undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Object 6)
  - Sketch or print: "Proposed Building for the Catholic Club…", undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Object 7)
  - Sketch or print: George Washington at Mt. Vernon, undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Object 8)
  - Certificate awarded to Thomas Riggs Jr., undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Object 9)
  - Woodcut: Rodin portrait by Rene Cheruy; incudes handwritten note, newspaper portfolio, undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Object 10)
  - Framed pen and ink political cartoon: Alaska and Philippines personified, undated; Series 2 (Box 21, Object 11)
  - R.C. Riggs memo book, 1923; Series 2 (Box 22, Object 1)
    Contains 1942 letter from Thomas Riggs Jr.
  - Memorial document: "In Memoriam" Elisha Francis Riggs, 1911; Series 2 (Box 22, Object 2)
  - Long pipe, undated; Series 2 (Box 23, Object 1)
  - Short pipe, undated; Series 2 (Box 23, Object 2)
  - Pocket watch, undated; Series 2 (Box 23, Object 3)
  - Small case, orange, undated; Series 2 (Box 23, Object 4)
  - Binoculars, undated; Series 2 (Box 23, Object 6)
  - Ornate smoking pipe, undated; Series 2 (Box 23, Object 29)
  - Medic armband worn by Thomas Lawrason Riggs in WWI, undated; Series 2 (Box 24, Object 5)
  - Wooden doll/ photograph cut-out: unidentified man, undated; Series 2 (Box 24, Object 6)
  - White leather gloves, undated; Series 2 (Box 24, Object 7)
  - Map of German river, undated; Series 2 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Paper documents, circa 1785 - 2006; Series 3; 3 Linear Feet
  Paper documents include draft manuscripts, correspondence, newspaper clippings, and formal documents. The bulk of the material dates between circa 1870 – circa 1940. The draft manuscripts consist of multiple drafts of "The Riggs Family of Maryland: a Genealogical and Historical Record" by John Beverley Riggs and a single draft of "Remarks on Some of the Oldest Maps in America" by Frederic Kunstmann. Correspondence represents invitation acceptances to dinner hosted by Mr. and Mrs. George Washington Riggs Jr., a letter sent to Lawrason Riggs, photocopies of Elisha Riggs Jr. letters, and letters between E. Francis Riggs Sr. and The Mount Vernon Ladies Association. Newspaper clippings and formal documents (awards, proclamations) primarily relate to Thomas Riggs Jr., Governor of Alaska.
  Organized into 5 subseries: Correspondence, Personal business, Publications and research, Diaries, and Paper documents (original donation).
  - Correspondence, 1832-2006; 1942-1950; Series 3 Subseries 1; 6.25 Linear Feet 12 document boxes 1 slim document box
    Correspondence to and from John Beverley Riggs are arranged chronologically. Correspondences to and from Thomas (Tommy) Riggs, Jr. are arranged in original order.
    This subseries includes hand or type written letters to and from John Beverley Riggs, Thomas Riggs, Sr., and Thomas (Tommy) Riggs, Jr. by Riggs family members. The majority of letters to John Beverley Riggs are from his mother, Mrs. Lawrason B. Riggs, and his sister, Mrs. John E. Muncaster, Jr. (Eleanor). The materials date from 1832 – 1990, with the bulk of the material ranging from 1942 – 1950.
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1938 September 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 27)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1939 March 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 28)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1939 May 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 29)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1940 July 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 30)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1941 February 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 31)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 April 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 37, Folder 32)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      Includes a newsclipping about John Beverley Riggs cousin, Lisette Riggs, engagement.
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 November 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 December 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 December 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 11)
      Letter is dated 1942 December 3 but envelope is post marked 1943 January.
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 December 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 December 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 December 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 December 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 December 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 December 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1942 December 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 January 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 36)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 37)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 38)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 February 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 39)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 40)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 41)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 42)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 43)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 44)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 45)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 46)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 47)
      Includes newsclipping about Lisette Riggs wedding (John Beverley Riggs' cousin)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 48)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 March 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 49)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 April 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 50)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 April 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 51)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 April 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 52)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 April 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 53)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 April 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 54)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 55)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 56)
      Includes newsclipping of the death announcement of Reverend Thomas Lawrason Riggs 1943 April 26
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 57)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 58)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 59)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 60)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 61)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 62)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 63)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 64)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 65)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 May 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 66)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 67)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 68)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 69)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 30, Folder 70)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 June 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 July 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 July 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 July 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 July 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 July 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 August 1; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 August 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 August 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 August 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 August 22; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 August 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 August 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 September 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 September 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 September 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 September 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 September 26; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 27)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 October 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 November 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 November 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 November 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 November 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 November 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 November 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 December 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 December 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 December 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 December 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 December 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 43)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 December 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 44)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1943 December 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 45)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 January 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 46)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 January 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 47)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 January 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 48)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 January 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 49)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 January 16; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 50)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 January 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 51)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 January 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 52)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 January 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 53)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 January 30; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 54)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 6; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 55)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 56)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 57)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 11; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 58)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 59)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 60)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 21; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 61)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 62)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 February 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 63)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 64)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 65)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 66)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 67)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 68)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 69)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 31, Folder 70)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 March 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 April 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 April 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 April 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 April 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 April 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 April 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 April 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 April 23; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 May 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 May 9; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 May 15; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 May 18; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 May 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 May 28; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 May 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 June 4; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 June 12; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 June 19; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 July 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 July 27; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 July 31; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 August 2; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 August 5; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 August 7; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 August 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 August 14; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 August 20; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 August 25; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 September 3; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 September 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 September 10; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 September 13; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 September 17; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 September 24; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 September 29; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 October 1; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - Letters to John Beverley Riggs, 1944 October 8; Series 3 Subseries 1 (Box 32, Folder 39)